{"message": "Successfully uploaded", "questions": [{"explanation": "Answer: tied", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past tense).", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["a", "tied", "and", "hunters"]}, {"explanation": "take is Verb (base form)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (base form) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to _____________ him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["help", "go", "let", "take"]}, {"explanation": "lifted is Verb (past tense)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (past tense) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he _____________ his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["was", "tied", "went", "lifted"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: later", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adverb.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["the", "tied", "a", "later"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: by", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["lion", "idea", "let", "by"]}, {"explanation": "went is Verb (past tense)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (past tense) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they _____________ in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["tied", "went", "was", "lifted"]}, {"explanation": "by is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled _____________ the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["that", "after", "by", "in"]}, {"explanation": "lion is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the _____________ , and tied him to a tree .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["tree", "wagon", "lion", "paw"]}, {"explanation": "that is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After _____________ they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["of", "that", "after", "in"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: in", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["the", "take", "in", "went"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: and", "question": "In the following sentence identify Coordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["mouse", "to", "idea", "and"]}, {"explanation": "go is Verb (base form)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (base form) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him _____________ .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["go", "help", "take", "let"]}], "success": 1}